mainadv.com 2016-11-21

# Privacy Policy - MainAd

**MainAd is the trading name of mainADV S.R.L** and is firmly committed to protect the privacy of Internet users as well as to foster user confidence in the Internet, online advertising and direct marketing.

We continuously evaluate innovative ways to protect online user privacy while also offering our clients the ability to own and use information regarding interactions with their customers.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to provide users with clear and complete notification about the user information we collect in connection with our services and corporate website.

**– Information We Collect Through our Services**  
**We do not collect PII.**  
We do not collect the online user’s personally identifiable information (“PII”) through our services. PII generally refers to information such as an individual’s name, mailing address, phone number or e-mail address.

**Non-Personal Information Collected by our Services**  
We offer a wide range of services that allow advertisers and publishers to show online users the most useful and relevant ads online.

We may collect non-personally identifiable information (“Non-PII”) regarding the user’s behavior and usage patterns on advertisements and sites operated by our clients to better customize the type of advertisements users see on various sites.

Non-PII may include information such as the type of Internet browser used by an online user, the type of computer operating system used, the domain name of the website visited, as well as information related to websites and web pages a user is viewing when an advertisement is shown.

We collect Non-PII through the use of cookies and pixels. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. A cookie is a file placed on certain pages that uniquely identifies your browser. A pixel is a line of code which is used by a website or third party ad server to track a user’s activity.

The use of a pixel allows us to record information when a user has visited a particular webpage along with the additional Non-PII that the website publisher or advertiser may choose to include with the pixel.

We encourage you to always read the privacy policies of the websites you visit to understand the issues relating to your online privacy.

The use of cookies by our affiliates, service providers or tracking utility company is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

We do not have access or control over these cookies. Third parties use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate through our site.

**– Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**  
We do not collect PII via our services; therefore, we do not sell, rent, or share PII collected on our customer’s websites to affiliated or non-affiliated third parties.

We may disclose Non-PII collected through our services and information derived from it, to our customers. This Non-PII may be used by our customers to deliver tailored ads to users on participating websites. We shall not use this information to contact or identify any person individually. Furthermore, all of our customers have warranted that they shall use any Non-PII they receive in compliance with applicable laws and regulations, but we shall not be responsible for any breach of any such warranty by customers.

We may disclose a user’s information to the competent authorities when we reasonably believe that we are obligated by law to do so, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including, but not limited to fraud as well as situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Furthermore, we may disclose a user’s information in order to establish, exercise, or defend our legal rights for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk.

**– Extended Cookie Policy**

We use technology (which includes cookies) in the delivery of our services.  
Cookies are small pieces of text used to store information on web browsers. Cookies are used to store and receive identifiers and other information on computers, phones, and other devices. Other technologies, including data we store on your web browser or device, identifiers associated with your device, and other software, are used for similar purposes. In this policy, we refer to all of these technologies as “cookies.”

We use cookies to provide you with the best experience possible, and to better understand how people use our services so that we can improve them.  
Cookies help us provide, protect and improve services, such as by personalizing content, tailoring and measuring ads, and providing a safer experience.  
We use cookies to understand and analyze the usage trends of our users on our corporate website. We do not collect the online user’s PII through these cookies — only non-PII. 

We use cookies to help us show ads for businesses and other organizations to people who may be interested in the products, services or causes they promote.  
For example: Cookies allow us to help deliver ads to people who have previously visited a business’s website, purchased its products or used its apps. Cookies also allow us to limit the number of times that you see an ad so you don’t see the same ad over and over again.

We also use cookies to help measure the performance of ad campaigns for businesses that use our services.

Cookies also allow us to provide insights about the people who use our services, as well as, the people who interact with the ads, websites, and apps of our advertisers and the businesses that use our services.

You can delete MainAd.com cookies by [clicking here](http://mainad.com/optout.php).

OTHER THIRD PARTY COOKIES  
In our websites, third parties may also set their own anonymous cookies, for the purposes of tracking the success of their application, or customizing the application for you. Because of how cookies work, we cannot access these cookies, nor can the third parties access the data in cookies used by us.  
To understand how other parties use cookies, please review their policies.

HOW DO I DISABLE COOKIES?  
If you want to disable cookies you need to change your website browser settings to reject cookies. How to do this will depend on the browser you use and we provide further detail below on how to disable cookies for the most popular browsers:  
[Internet Explorer](http://windows.microsoft.com/it-it/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies);  
[Safari](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=it_IT&locale=en_US);  
[Mozilla Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/it/kb/Attivare%20e%20disattivare%20i%20cookie);  
[Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=it&p=cpn_cookies);

WHAT HAPPENS IF I DISABLE COOKIES?  
This depends on which cookies you disable, but in general the site may not operate properly if cookies are switched off. 

**– Data Retention**  
We maintain Non-PII on users for a period of thirteen months. This data includes web sites visited, content viewed, ad interaction, IP addresses, browser type and language settings. We may maintain Non-PII in an aggregated form for all of our Services for a period longer than thirteen months. In the event that any PII is recieved for any purpose or purposes, such PII shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.

**– Information Security**  
We endeavour to follow generally accepted industry standards to protect against the unauthorized access, retention and disclosure of data. Any data that is stored on our servers is treated as confidential information. Please keep in mind, however, that despite reasonable efforts to protect data on our servers, no method of transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your data at all times, we cannot guarantee its absolute security and shall not be liable for any breach of security by an outside party.

**– Change to this Privacy Policy**  
Please note that because of the changing nature of privacy laws, user needs, and our business, we may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time without the consent of users by providing advance notice on our Web site before implementing such modifications. Accordingly, since we want to help you clearly understand our Privacy Policy and any pertinent revisions, we encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically to become aware of any changes that may have occurred.

**– Your Use and Correspondence on this Site**  
If you provide us information through our “Contact us” link in our corporate website, we will keep a record of the information you provide including your email address and any other personal information you provide solely for the purpose of responding to your inquiry or to provide you with requested marketing material.

This information will never be shared with third parties without your consent.

**– Linking to Other Sites**  
A link from our corporate website to another website does not imply our endorsement of that site. We do not control the sites to which we are linked and we assume no responsibility for their content or privacy policies.

It is strongly advised you should carefully review the privacy policies that apply to any sites you access from our site.

**– Spam and E-mail lists**  
We do not intentionally send unsolicited e-mail messages that could be construed as spam.

**– Questions or Comments about this Privacy Policy**  
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us through email. You can address your general questions and comments by e-mail: to [privacy@mainad.com](mailto:privacy@mainad.com) or by mail: **Attn: Legal Department. MainAd SRL, Piazza Alessandrini, n°25, 65127 Pescara, Italy.**
